const questionBank = [
  {
    question: `What is the fundamental principle of fat loss?`,
    options: [
      '1. Calories In, Calories Out',
      '2. First Law of Thermodynamics Application',
      '3. Both 1 and 2',
      '4. Neither 1 and 2',
    ],
    answer: '3',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which among them is a wrong statement?',
    options: [
      '1. Fat loss works on first law of thermodynamics',
      '2. Fat is release from the body in the form of heat energy',
      '3. Calories in, calories out is the fundamental principle of fat loss',
      '4. If you eat in calorie surplus, you will store fat in your body',
    ],
    answer: '2',
  },
  {
    question: 'How is fat release from the body?',
    options: [
      '1. Majorly in the form of Carbon Dioxide when we exhale, and then some water',
      '2. In the form of heat energy',
      '3. In the form of magic!',
      '4. Both 1 and 2',
    ],
    answer: '1',
  },
  {
    question: 'Choose the correct option.',
    options: [
      '1. You cannot spot reduce fat',
      '2. You can spot build muscle',
      '3. You can spot reduce fat',
      '4. Both 1 and 2',
    ],
    answer: '4',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which factor determines what part of body fat you lose first?',
    options: [
      '1. Genetics',
      '2. Type of Exercise',
      '3. Type of Diet',
      '4. Both 1 and 2',
    ],
    answer: '1',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which is the major factor of fat loss journey?',
    options: [
      '1. Nutrition',
      '2. Exercise',
      '3. Junk Food',
      '4. Neither 1 and 2',
    ],
    answer: '1',
  },
  {
    question: 'On what factors does weight depends on?',
    options: [
      '1. Fat',
      '2. Fat + Muscle',
      '3. Fat + Muscle + Water + Bone Density',
      '4. Fat + Muscle + Water + Bone Density + Mensuration Cycle (for women)',
    ],
    answer: '4',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which factor is more important in fat loss?',
    options: [
      '1. Insulin control',
      '2. Calorie deficit diet',
      '3. Both 1 and 2',
      '4. Neither 1 and 2',
    ],
    answer: '2',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which is true?',
    options: [
      '1. You can eat as much as you want if you are on intermittent fasting schedule because insulin',
      '2. You have to eat in calorie deficit regardless for fat loss',
      '3. You can eat as many times as you want in a day if you are in calorie deficit to lose weight',
      '4. Both 2 and 3',
    ],
    answer: '4',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which activities results in Autophagy?',
    options: [
      '1. Exercise',
      '2. Fasting',
      '3. It happens automatically',
      '4. All three',
    ],
    answer: '4',
  },
];

module.exports = questionBank;
